<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Leow Kah Man - Tech Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.leowkahman.com/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Leow Kah Man - Tech Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Except as otherwise noted, the content of this page is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License, code samples are licensed under the MIT License. Third-party product names and logos may be the trademarks of their respective owners.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 03:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.leowkahman.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.leowkahman.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 03:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.leowkahman.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This Privacy Policy informs you of our privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way information about you, including from your online activity is collected and how that information is used by our site. This privacy policy link is readily available at the bottom of every web page on this website.
At www.leowkahman.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our siteu, and how we safeguard your information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.leowkahman.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 18:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.leowkahman.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Leow Kah Man, a Software Architect and Full Stack Software Developer, lives in Malaysia, likes just about anything that has to do with technology.
Designing cloud architectures that drive new innovations, raise scalability and reduce time to deploy is what I am passionate about. I believe microservice infrastructure is the most efficient way to scale, have high availability and ease of maintenance.
During my spare time, I like tinkering with OpenWRT and Raspberry Pi, and trying out new cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.leowkahman.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 18:54:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.leowkahman.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please comment on posts if you have questions regarding a specific post.
For general matters, you may contact me preferably by sending a private message via Facebook or dropping me a message via the contact form below:
Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>